JACKSON MORI

Blockchain Engineer

SUMMARY

Dedicated Blockchain/Web developer specialized in Cosmos SDK, Golang, Rust, Cosmwasm, Solana, and Solidity. I have rich experience in building chain using Cosmos SDK and writing smart contracts using Rust/Cosmwasm. Developed the token bridge chain Built NFT market place project and Defi project on Terra, Juno, Ethereum and Binance. Implementation/deployment in both frontend & backend sides integration frontend with SC. Work experiences with startups for over years, helping to build technology-based businesses from the ground up.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Blockchain Engineer

03/2021 - 01/2023

Humans.ai Remote

- Built token bridge chain which enables users to transfer tokens from Ethereum to
- Added observer module which tracks the transaction from Ethereum and the Cosmos chain.
- Added IBC relayer.

our chain

- Wrote smart contracts on Cosmos chain for the pool using Cosmwasm.
- · Built NFT marketplace on the chain using Cosmwasm.

Lead Blokchain Engineer

07/2019 - 02/2021

INSTACOIN Remote

- Developed token and DEX platform on Ethereum network.
- · Extended the DEX platform onto Polygon.
- Developed a bridge to cross-operate the token on multiplenetworks.
- · Integrated contract using web3.js.
- Developed wrapped token and DEX platform using project-serumon Solana network.

Full-Stack Developer

02/2016 - 04/2019

FUNNELAIR Remote

- Led the front-end development of a smart price recommendations platform used by large retail and eCommerce clients.
- · Implemented and managed companies' Design System library.
- Profiled critical components, eliminating wasting renders which dramatically improved performance.
- Simplified the project structure, emphasizing reusability and scalability.

Frontend Developer

10/2014 - 12/2015

Endertech Remote

- Worked on the development of multiple ecommerce websites, creating user interfaces and developing reusable components in frameworks such as React.js, Vue.js and AngularJS.
- Managed version control using Git and collaborated with project managers to created ocumentation and QA plans for software applications.
- Developed and maintained complex web applications using JavaScript frameworks and libraries such as JQuery, React.js and Vue.js integrating with back-end servers through RESTful APIs.

RECENT PROJECTS

https://www.marbledao.finance/

https://xsurge.net/

https://nft.rdland.io

https://app.hashflow.com

https://cyberdreamers.io

EXPERTISE

Cosmos SDK/ Golang

Cosmwasm/Rust

CosmJS

Solidity

React

NodeJS

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

University of Manitoba 04/2010 - 03/2014

LANGUAGES

Japanese

Native

English

Proficient

••••